bollywoodgo.net 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy - BollywoodGo.NET

We do not collection your information however, third-parties like our blog hosting company "Google Inc.", Our blog stats tracking tool "Google Analytics" , Our advertising networks "Google AdSense" may collect your information via;

 **Cookies.** A cookie is a message that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.Third-parties may use cookies to assist in (a) helping you stay logged on the Site (b) providing video recommendations.

 **IP Address.** An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you use the Internet. We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration, server problem diagnosis and to compile aggregate information (such as how many visitors visited the Site and their approximate geographic locations). When you visit a particular Web page on the Site, our servers log your IP address. We analyze aggregated user traffic information to improve the quality of the user-experience.

 **1\. Your Role in Protecting Your Privacy**  
Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online. Without limitation of the foregoing,please keep your username and password private and safe.

 **2\. Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
If you use the BollywoodGo.NET, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the BollywoodGo.NET. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Sites or the BollywoodGo.NET after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on the site will constitute your acceptance of those changes.
